

# ARTHUR FLORENÇO

Full Stack Developer



<u>LinkedIn</u>

arthur.florenco@outlook.com



<u>Portugal</u>

# **PROFILE**

I work as a freelancer creating beautiful and intuitive interfaces for my clients. My user-centered approach and ability to think holistically allow me to develop robust and intuitive software that takes the user experience to the next level.

## PORTFOLIO

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Portuguese Mother tongue
- English Intermediate
- Spanish Intermediate

### DIGITAL SKILLS

- React
- JavaScript (ES6)
- PHP
- Node
- HTML/CSS
- MySQL
- Bootstrap
- iQuery
- Git e GitHub
- WordPress

- Angular JS
- Tailwind
- ASP.NET
- **Typescript**
- Vue JS
- SASS
- AWS
- PostCSS
- Rest

#### SKILLS

- · Problem solving;
- · Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills;
- · Adaptability;
- Able to handle several tasks at once;
- Initiative and empathy;
- · Ability to evaluate information objectively, analyze issues in depth and make informed decisions;
- Group work;
- Working under pressure;

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Freelancer

09/2023 - Present

- Creating the coding that brings a website to life and helping it to function as required by the host;
- Designing not only the layout of a website, but also how it works for the end user;
- Taking responsibility for the functions that can be performed when a user accesses the site;
- Using the latest mechanisms and applications to keep the site running as smoothly and efficiently as possible;
- · Testing new and existing sites and correcting any errors that may arise.

#### Automation technician

Scenerio Automation | 01/2018 - 06/2023

- Development of customized home automation projects based on customer requirements.
- Configuring automation systems to ensure their efficient operation according to the client's preferences.
- Installation of equipment such as sensors, controllers, security devices, audio and video systems, smart thermostats, among others.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Web Developer FullStack

Master D 2023 - Present

#### **Bachelor's Degree in Engineering**

PUC-RJ 2022 - 2022

# FURTHER EDUCATION

- Web Developer Full Stack 2024 Coursera
- Web Designs Responsive 2023 FreeCodeCamp
- Algorithms and Data Structures in JavaScript 2023 Odin Project
- Front-End Development Libraries 2023 Udemy
- Data Visualization 2023 FreeCodeCamp
- Legacy Algorithms and Data Structures in JavaScript 2023 -FreeCodeCamp